quoteroller.com 2019-07-11

# Privacy Policy - Quote Roller

_Last Updated: October 2, 2014_

Quote Roller, Inc. (the “Company”) is committed to maintaining robust privacy protections for its users. Our Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) is designed to help you understand how we collect, use and safeguard the information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our Website.

For purposes of this Agreement, “Website” refers to the Company’s service which can be accessed via our website at www.quoteroller.com which is further described in our [Terms of Use](http://www.quoteroller.com/terms-of-service/). The terms “we,” “us,” and “our” refer to the Company. “You” refers to you, as a user of The Website. By accepting our Privacy Policy and [Terms of Use](http://www.quoteroller.com/terms-of-service/), you consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.

**I. INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

We collect “Non-Personal Information” and “Personal Information.” Non-Personal Information includes information that cannot be used to personally identify you, such as anonymous usage data, general demographic information we may collect, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform types, preferences you submit and preferences that are generated based on the data you submit and number of clicks. “Personal Information” is information which can be used it identify you as an individual on its own when used for its intended purpose by The Company; at present, this includes only your email, which you submit to us through the registration process at the Site.

_**1\. Information collected via Technology**_  
To activate the Website you do not need to submit any Personal Information other than your name, general geographic location, profession or industry that you operate in and email address. You may also submit more details about your business like the name of your company. In an effort to improve the quality of the Website, we track information provided to us by your browser or by our software application when you view or use the Website, such as the website you came from (known as the “referring URL”), the type of browser you use, the device from which you connected to the Website, the time and date of access, and other information that does not personally identify you. We track this information using cookies, or small text files which include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to a user’s browser from our servers and are stored on the user’s computer hard drive. Sending a cookie to a user’s browser enables us to collect Non-Personal information about that user and keep a record of the user’s preferences when utilizing our services, both on an individual and aggregate basis. For example, the Company may use cookies to store the following information: session data, email address, username, and preferences. The Company may use both persistent and session cookies; persistent cookies remain on your computer after you close your session and until you delete them, while session cookies expire when you close your browser.

**_2\. Information you provide us by registering for an account_**  
In addition to the information provided automatically by your browser when you visit the Site, to become a subscriber to the Website you may need to provide us with Personal information we use to populate that profile. By registering, you are authorizing us to collect, store and use your email address in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

If you use a social networking site (“SNS”) account information to sign in to the Website, we will collect and store your SNS user ID. The privacy practices of the entity which generated such an SNS User ID are set forth in such entities Privacy Policy, and The Company has no control over the uses of your ID by such parties.

**_3\. Information your provide by contributing to the Website_**  
You may also provide us information in User Content (as defined in the Terms of Use) you post to the Website. Your questions, answers, and other contributions on the Website, and metadata about them (such as when you posted them), are publicly viewable on the Website, along with your name (unless the Website permits you to post anonymously). This information may be searched by search engines and be republished elsewhere on the Web in accordance with our Terms of Website. By using the Website, you consent to such public usage.

**_4\. Information you provide by completing online forms to request services from other Users._**  
In order to use the Website you may need to provide us with certain information via online forms. Some of the information submitted to the Company may be visible or communicated to additional Company representation. We do this to ensure quality control of User Content. Therefore, this information is not considered confidential and the user should not assume that such information is confidential. We will not, however, sell or distribute the information obtained in any User Content submitted to other Users by via our online forms. The Company is under no obligation to keep any information communicated to the Company confidential.

**_5\. Information you send to other Users._**  
This Privacy Policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. If you disclose your information to other parties using the Website or visit other websites linked on the Website or provided to you by other Users, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them. Since the Company does not control the privacy policies of third parties, or other individuals’ actions, you are subject to the privacy policies of that third party or those individuals. We encourage you to be sure the recipients are authenticated to your satisfaction before you send them any documents or sensitive information.

**II. HOW WE USE AND SHARE INFORMATION**

**_Personal Information:_**  
Except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, we do not sell, trade, rent or otherwise share for marketing purposes your Personal Information with third parties without your consent. We do share Personal Information with vendors who are performing services for the Company, such as the servers for our email communications who are provided access to user’s email address for purposes of sending emails from us. We may share Personal Information such as your name, billing address, and credit card number with vendors who assist us with payment processing. Our vendors are contractually obligated to use your Personal Information only at our direction and in accordance with our Privacy Policy.

In general, the Personal Information you provide to us is used to help us communicate with you. For example, we use Personal Information to contact users in response to questions, solicit feedback from users, provide technical support, and inform users about promotional offers.

**_Non-Personal Information_**  
In general, the Personal Information you provide to us is used to help us facilitate your use of the Website and communicate with you. For example, we use Personal Information to contact users in response to questions, solicit feedback from users, provide technical support, and inform users about promotional offers.

The Company may allow third-party ad servers or ad networks to serve advertisements on the Website. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the Website. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or web beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content. The Website does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent. However, please note that if an advertiser asks the Company to show an advertisement to a certain audience and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they are trying to reach. This Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, third-party advertisers. Please consult the respective privacy policies of such advertisers for more information.

We also use a third party service provider to help us process payments through the Website. Such third parties may have access to your Personal information, including credit card number, name, and physical address, as a result of providing these services to The Company.

In the event we undergo a business transaction such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, your Personal Information may be among the assets transferred or examined during the due diligence process. You acknowledge and consent that such transfers may occur and are permitted by this Privacy Policy, and that any acquirer of our assets may continue to process your Personal Information as set forth in this Privacy Policy. If our information practices change at any time in the future, we will post the policy changes to the Site so that you may opt out of the new information practices. We suggest that you check the Site periodically if you are concerned about how your information is used.

**III. HOW WE PROTECT INFORMATION**

We implement security measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access. Your account is protected by your account password and we urge you to take steps to keep your personal information safe by not disclosing your password and by logging out of your account after each use. We further protect your information from potential security breaches by implementing certain technological security measures including encryption, firewalls and secure socket layer technology. However, these measures do not guarantee that your information will not be accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed by breach of such firewalls and secure server software. In addition, while we take reasonable measure to ensure that other entities who provide us with payment processing services keep your information confidential and secure, such entities’ practices are ultimately beyond our control. By using our Website, you acknowledge that you understand and agree to assume these risks.

**IV. CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY**

The Company reserves the right to change this policy and our Terms of Use at any time, and such changes will take effect immediately. You should periodically check the Website and this page for updates.

**V. CONTACT US**

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy or the practices of this Website, please [contact us](http://www.quoteroller.com/contact-us/) by sending us an email.
